Wauregan and Quinebaug Company Records 1981.0010
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series II: Correspondence, 1866-1963
  - Subseries B: Comptroller's Office Correspondence, 1942-1953
    - Webbley, F.W.
      - C. F. Hathaway and Company, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 256)
      - McCampbell and Company, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 257-258)
      - Turner Halsey Company, 1953 (Box 52, Folder 259-260)
  - Subseries C: Alexander Maino's Correspondence, 1949-1954
    - A, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 261)
    - Applications, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 262)
    - American Yarn and Processing Company, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 263)
    - A, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 264)
    - B, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 265)
    - C, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 266)
    - D, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 267-268)
    - E, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 269)
    - F, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 270)
    - Franklin Process Company, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 271)
    - G, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 272-273)
    - H, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 274)
    - H - I, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 275)
    - I- J, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 276)
    - L, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 277)
    - M, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 278)
    - N, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 279)
    - Nashawena, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 280)
    - O, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 281)
    - P, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 282)
    - P, U, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 283)
    - R, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 284)
    - S, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 285)
    - T, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 286)
    - U, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 287)
    - W, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 288)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 289)
    - Franklin Process Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 290)
    - G, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 291)
    - H, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 292)
    - I, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 293)
    - J, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 294)
    - K, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 295)
    - L, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 296)
    - M, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 297)
    - McCampbell and Company, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 298)
    - N, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 299)
    - O, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 300)
    - P, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 301)
    - R, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 302)
    - S, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 303)
    - T, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 304)
    - U, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 305)
    - V, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 306)
    - W, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 307)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 308)
    - A, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 309)
    - B, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 310)
    - C, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 311)
    - D, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 312)
    - E, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 313)
    - F, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 314)
    - Franklin Process Company, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 315-316)
    - G, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 317)
    - H, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 318)
    - I, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 319)
    - J, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 320)
    - L, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 321)
    - M, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 322)
    - McCampbell and Company, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 323-324)
    - N, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 325)
    - P, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 326)
    - R, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 327)
    - S, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 328)
    - T, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 329)
    - U, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 330)
    - W, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 331)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 332)
    - FISBA Costs, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 333)
    - Turner Halsey Company, 1953 (Box 53, Folder 334-335)
  - Subseries D: Gordon Harrower's Correspondence, 1924-1963
    - General, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 336-338)
    - General, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 339-341)
    - Unidentified, 1924-1925 (Box 53, Folder 342)
    - General, 1941-1942 (Box 53, Folder 343)
    - Alligator Company, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 344-345)
    - American Cotton Manufacturers Institute, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 346-347)
    - American Thread Company, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 348)
    - American Viscose Company, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 349)
    - Atwood, J.A., III, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 350)
    - A, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 351)
    - Banco, Inc., 1950 (Box 53, Folder 352)
    - Bradford Dyeing Association, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 353)
    - Brooks Brothers, 1950 (Box 2:53, Folder 354)
    - Bullard, Edward J., 1950 (Box 53, Folder 355)
    - B, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 356)
    - Comery, Davison, and Jacobson, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 357)
    - Comery, Davison, and Jacobson, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 358)
    - C, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 359)
    - E.I. DuPont DeNemours and Company, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 360)
    - D, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 361)
    - E, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 362)
    - Flynn, George D., Jr., 1950 (Box 53, Folder 363)
    - Folkard and Lawrence, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 364)
    - Foreign Trade Commission, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 365-370)
    - F, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 371)
    - G, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 372)
    - C.F. Hathaway Company, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 373)
    - Hinckly, Allen, Tillinghast & Wheeler, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 374)
    - H, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 375)
    - Institute of Textile Technology, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 376-377)
    - International Statistical Bureau, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 378)
    - William Iselin and Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 54, Folder 379)
    - I, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 380)
    - J, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 381)
    - K, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 382)
    - Langdon, Duncan, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 383)
    - Henry Lewis and Company, Inc., 1950 (Box 54, Folder 384)
    - Lynch, Francis E., 1950 (Box 54, Folder 385)
    - L, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 386)
    - Manufacturers Mutual Fire Insurance Company, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 387)
    - Martin, Edward E.I., 1950 (Box 54, Folder 388)
    - M, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 389)
    - McCampbell and Company, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 390-394)
    - Mc, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 395)
    - Memoranda, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 396)
    - N, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 397)
    - O, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 398)
    - Providence National Bank, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 399)
    - P, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 400)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 401-402)
    - Reports, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 403)
    - Rhode Island Hospital Trust Company, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 404)
    - R, 1950 (Box 405, Folder 405)
    - S, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 406)
    - Textile Committee on Public Relations, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 407-410)
    - T, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 411)
    - U, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 412)
    - Woodbridge, Henry, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 413)
    - W, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 414-415)
    - X - Z, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 416)
    - Alligator Company, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 417)
    - American Cotton Manufacturers Institute, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 418-420)
    - Foreign Trade Committee, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 421-427)
    - Association of Textile Merchants of New York, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 428-429)
    - Atwood, J.A., III, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 430)
    - A, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 431)
    - Bradford Dyeing Association, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 432)
    - Brooks Brothers, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 433)
    - Budget Sheet, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 434)
    - Cash Forecast-Actuals, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 435)
    - Cash Requirements, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 436)
    - Comery, Davison and Jacobson, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 437)
    - Connecticut, State of, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 438)
    - C, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 439)
    - D, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 440)
    - E, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 441)
    - Fine Combed Goods Industry Advisory Comm., 1950 (Box 56, Folder 442)
    - Flynn, George D., Jr., 1951 (Box 56, Folder 443)
    - F, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 444)
    - G, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 445)
    - C.F. Hathaway Company, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 446)
    - Hinckley, Allen, Salisbury and Parsons, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 447)
    - H, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 448)
    - Invitations to Bid, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 449-450)
    - William Iselin & Company, Inc., 1951 (Box 56, Folder 451-452)
    - I, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 453)
    - J, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 454)
    - K, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 455)
    - Langdon, Duncan, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 456)
    - Lynch, Francis E., 1951 (Box 56, Folder 457)
    - L, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 458)
    - Manufacturers Mutual Fire Insurance Company, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 459)
    - M, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 460)
    - McCampbell and Company, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 461-463)
    - Mc, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 464)
    - Memoranda, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 465)
    - N, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 466)
    - O, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 467)
    - Providence Union Bank & Trust Company, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 468)
    - P, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 469)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 470)
    - Reports, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 471)
    - Rhode Island Hospital Trust Company, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 472)
    - R, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 473)
    - Salisbury, Harold P., 1951 (Box 56, Folder 474)
    - Stockholders, Letters to, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 475)
    - S, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 476)
    - Textile Committee for Public Relations, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 477-478)
    - Thomas D. Troy & Company, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 479)
    - Turner Halsey Company, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 480)
    - T, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 481)
    - United States Marine Corps, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 482)
    - United States Quartermaster Procurement Agency, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 483)
    - U, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 484)
    - Woodbridge, Henry, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 485)
    - General, 1951-1955 (Box 56, Folder 486)
    - Boss and Wachtel, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 487)
    - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1952 (Box 57, Folder 488)
    - Small Business Administration, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 489)
    - Special File, 1954 (Box 57, Folder 490)
    - General, 1954-1955 (Box 57, Folder 491)
    - General, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 492)
    - Small Business Administration, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 493)
    - L.F. Dommerich & Company, Inc., 1954, 1957-1959 (Box 57, Folder 494)
    - L.F. Dommerich & Company, Inc., 1956 (Box 57, Folder 495)
    - General, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 496-497)
    - Small Business Administration, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 498)
    - Textile Workers Union of America, 1956 (Box 57, Folder 499)
    - Tuner Halsey Company, Inc., 1956 (Box 57, Folder 500)
    - Memoranda, 1956-1957 (Box 58, Folder 501)
    - General, 1956-1957 (Box 58, Folder 502)
    - Wasserman and Taten, 1956-1957 (Box 58, Folder 503)
    - Directors, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 504)
    - L.F. Dommerich & Company, Inc., 1957 (Box 58, Folder 505)
    - General, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 506)
    - Wauregan Mills Textile Operations discontinued, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 507)
    - Sale of machinery, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 508)
    - Small Business Administration, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 509-511)
    - Water Expense, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 512)
    - Water Expense, 1957-1958 (Box 58, Folder 513)
    - General, 1957-1959 (Box 58, Folder 514)
    - Prospective Corporation Purchases, 1957-1959 (Box 58, Folder 515)
    - Mr. Meade's Correspondence, 1957-1961 (Box 58, Folder 516)
    - General, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 517)
    - Small Business Administration, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 518-520)
    - Small Business Administration, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 521-524)
    - Mr. Howland's Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 59, Folder 525)
    - General, undated (Box 59, Folder 526)
- Series III: General Accounts Records, 1853-1977
  - Subseries A: Journals, 1877-1973
    - 1877-1888 (Box 60)
    - 1878 (Box 61)
    - 1884-1889 (Box 62)
    - 1884-1890 (Box 63)
    - 1896-1897 (Box 64)
    - 1897-1899 (Box 77)
    - 1899-1903 (Box 78)
    - 1903-1906 (Box 76)
    - 1906-1910 (Box 72)
    - 1910-1914 (Box 79)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 65)
    - 1914-1916 (Box 80)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 68)
    - 1917-1922 (Box 66)
    - 1917-1924 (Box 67)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 69)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 70)
    - 1924-1929 (Box 71)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 73)
    - 1928-1934 (Box 75)
    - 1932 (Box 74)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 81)
    - 1951-1957 (Box 82)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 83)
    - Loose items from Wauregan general accounts journals, 1898-1932 (Box 457)
  - Subseries B: Cashbooks, 1880-1949
    - 1880-1886 (Box 94)
    - 1887-1893 (Box 95)
    - 1888-1898 (Box 87)
    - 1893-1898 (Box 84)
    - 1898-1899 (Box 85)
    - 1899-1906 (Box 86)
    - 1906-1913 (Box 92)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 88)
    - 1916-1921 (Box 89)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 90)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 96)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 97)
    - 1928 (Box 98)
    - 1929-1933 (Box 91)
    - 1939-1941 (Box 93)
    - 1943-1949 (Box 99)
    - N, 1971, 1977 (Box 442)
  - Subseries C: Ledgers, 1857-1934
    - 1857-1889 (Box 100)
    - 1863-1867 (Box 101)
    - 1863-1882 (Box 104)
    - 1864-1886 (Box 105)
    - 1867-1880 (Box 102)
    - 1868-1889 (Box 106)
    - 1869-1876 (Box 103)
    - 1877-1883 (Box 107)
    - 1882-1890 (Box 108)
    - 1887-1894 (Box 109)
    - 1888-1900 (Box 110)
    - 1894-1899 (Box 113)
    - 1894-1899 (Box 123)
    - 1899-1905 (Box 117)
    - 1899-1905 (Box 122)
    - 1899-1905 (Box 111)
    - 1905-1913 (Box 124)
    - 1906-1913 (Box 112)
    - 1910-1916 (Box 116)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 118)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 130)
    - 1916-1923 (Box 121)
    - 1919-1925 (Box 129)
    - 1922-1929 (Box 114)
    - 1924-1927 (Box 119)
    - 1925-1930 (Box 128)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 120)
    - 1929-1934 (Box 127)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 126)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 125)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 115)
  - Subseries D: Executive Account Records, 1877-1957
    - Trial Balances, 1889-1899, 1929-1938, 1950-1951 (Box 131, Folder 527)
    - Expense Accounts, 1945-1951 (Box 131, Folder 528)
    - Expense Accounts, 1952-1957 (Box 131, Box 529)
    - Mill Fund, 1877-1889 (Box 131, Folder 530)
    - Mill Fund, 1890 (Box 131, Folder 531)
    - Mill Fund, 1891 (Box 131, Folder 532)
  - Subseries E: Accounts Payable and Receivable, 1889-1972
    - Accounts Receivable and Payable, 1888-1893 (Box 131, Folder 533)
    - Accounts Receivable and Payable, 1899-1915 (Box 131, Box 534)
    - Accounts Receivable and Payable, 1914-1931 (Box 131, Folder 535)
    - Accounts Receivable and Payable, 1918-1934 (Box 131, Folder 536)
    - Accounts Receivable and Payable, 1954-1960 (Box 131, Folder 537)
    - Accounts Payable Ledger, 1963-1968 (Box 131, Folder 538-539)
    - Accounts Receivable, 1960-1972 (Box 131, Folder 540)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1966-1972 (Box 131, Folder 541)
    - Accounts Receivable Ledger, 1971-1972 (Box 131, Folder 542-543)
  - Subseries F: Statements, 1853-1875
    - Statements, 1855-1863 (Box 131)
    - Statements, 1864-1875 (Box 131)
  - Subseries G: Invoices, 1885-1905
    - 1885-1889 (Box 134)
    - 1889-1893 (Box 135)
    - 1892-1904 (Box 132)
    - 1894-1895 (Box 137)
    - 1895-1896 (Box 138)
    - 1895-1899 (Box 133)
    - 1916-1921 (Box 139)
    - 1947-1952 (Box 140)
    - 1949-1953 (Box 141)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 136)
    - Receipts and Invoices, 1885 (Box 429, Folder 5859)
    - Receipts and Invoices, 1889 (Box 429, Folder 5860)
    - Receipts and Invoices, 1890 (Box 429, Folder 5861)
    - Receipts and Invoices, 1891 (Box 429, Folder 5862)
- Series IV: Purchasing and Receiving Records, 1863-1957
  - Production Supply Invoices
    - Purchase Invoice Register, 1949-1952 (Box 142)
    - Completed Cotton Invoice Weight Sheets, 1945-1946 (Box 143)
    - Purchase Invoice Voucher Register Prepaid Insurance, 1943-1949 (Box 144)
  - Cotton Purchase Records
    - Baling Book #21, 1890-1893 (Box 154)
    - Baling Book, Transfer #1, 1957-1959 (Box 152)
    - Cotton Book #2, 1895-1901 (Box 145)
    - Cotton Book #3, 1901-1906 (Box 146)
    - Cotton Book #4, 1912-1915 (Box 147)
    - Cotton Book #5, 1916-1919 (Box 148)
    - Cotton Book #6, 1921-1925 (Box 149)
    - Cotton Book #7, 1926-1929 (Box 150)
    - Cotton Book #4, 1926-1933 (Box 156)
    - Cotton Book #8 (Box 151)
    - Cotton Purchase Journal, 1889-1896 (Box 153)
    - Cotton Purchase Journal, 1896-1898 (Box 155)
  - Cotton Sample Reports (Box 157, Folder 544)
  - Inventories
    - 1943 (Box 157, Folder 545)
    - 1944 (Box 157, Folder 546)
    - 1945 (Box 157, Folder 547)
    - 1946 (Box 157, Folder 548)
    - 1947 (Box 157, Folder 549-550)
    - 1948 (Box 157, Folder 551-552)
    - 1949 (Box 157, Folder 553-553a)
    - 1950 (Box 157, Folder 554)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 157, Folder 555-556)
    - 1951 (Box 157, Folder 557-558)
    - 1952 (Box 157, Folder 559)
    - November 1952 (Box 157, Folder 560)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 157, Folder 561)
    - 1956 (Box 157, Folder 562)
    - 1957 (Box 158, Folder 563)
    - 1952 March (Box 158, Folder 564)
  - Inventory of Finished Goods, 1948 (Box 159)
- Series V: Production Records, 1860-1965
  - Subseries A: Machinery, 1900-1960
    - 1900-1910 (Box 160, Folder 565)
    - 1911-1912 (Box 160, Folder 566)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 160, Folder 567)
    - 1915-1920 (Box 160, Folder 568)
    - 1921-1932 (Box 160, Folder 569)
    - 1942-1949 (Box 160, Folder 570-571)
    - 1955-1960 (Box 160, Folder 572)
    - Equipment Inventory, 1916-1922 (Box 161)
    - Equipment Inventory, 1920 (Box 162)
  - Subseries B: Machine Layouts, 1921, 1945, 1949, 1957 (Box not specified)
    - 1921 (Box 160, Folder 573)
    - 1945 (Box 160, Folder 574)
    - 1949 (Box 160, Folder 575)
    - 1957 (Box 160, Folder 576)
    - Layout Book, 1902-1912 (Box 163)
    - Layout Book, 1920-1925 (Box 164)
  - Subseries C: Supplies and Repairs, 1860-1959
    - 1860-1869 (Box 165, Folder 577)
    - 1870-1879 (Box 165, Folder 578)
    - 1880-1889 (Box 165, Folder 579)
    - 1890-1899 (Box 165, Folder 580)
    - 1900-1920 (Box 165, Folder 581)
    - 1943-1949 (Box 165, Folder 582)
    - 1950-1959 (Box 165, Folder 583)
    - Gas Ration records, 1943-1945 (Box 165, Folder 584)
    - Gas Ration records, 1943-1944 (Box 165, Folder 585)
    - Motor vehicle records, 1943-1946 (Box 165, Folder 586)
    - Account Book, 1893-1930 (Box 166)
    - Orders, 1949-1952 (Box 167)
    - Orders and Catalog, 1953-1954 (Box 165, Folder 587)
  - Subseries D: Engineering Studies, 1911-1965
    - Institute of Textile Technology, 1945-1946 (Box 165, Folder 588)
    - Institute of Textile Technology, 1947 (Box 165, Folder 589)
    - Lockwood, Greene & Co., 1911 (Box 165, Folder 590)
    - Lockwood, Greene & Co., 1912 (Box 165, Folder 591)
    - Ralph E. Loper Co., 1946 (Box 165, Folder 592)
    - Ralph E. Loper Co., 1947 (Box 165, Folder 593)
    - Ralph E. Loper Co., 1948 (Box 165, Folder 594)
    - Henry Souther Engineering Co., 1965 (Box 165, Folder 595)
  - Subseries E: Supply Catalogs, undated
    - A (Box 165, Folder 596-597)
    - B (Box 165, Folder 598)
    - Boilers (Box 165, Folder 599)
    - Boiler Feedwater (Box 165, Folder 600)
    - Bahnson Control (Box 168, Folder 601)
    - C (Box 168, Folder 602-603)
    - Comber Layout (Box 168, Folder 604)
    - Conveying Equipment (Box 168, Folder 605)
    - Coal (Box 168, Folder 606)
    - Crosby Steam and Valve Co. (Box 168, Folder 607)
    - Collins Wheel (Box 168, Folder 608)
    - Compressor and Aftercooler blueprints (Box 168, Folder 609)
    - Century Electric Co. (Box 168, Folder 610)
    - Cray Brothers (Box 168, Folder 611)
    - Crocker-Wheeler Co. (Box 168, Folder 612)
    - Cadman Manufacturing (Box 168, Folder 613)
    - D (Box 168, Folder 614)
    - E (Box 168, Folder 615)
    - F (Box 168, Folder 616-617)
    - G (Box 168, Folder 618-619)
    - G (Box 169, Folder 620-622)
    - H (Box 169, Folder 623-625)
    - Hartford Steam Boiler Co. (Box 169, Folder 626)
    - Humidifying System Blueprints (Box 169, Folder 627)
    - I (Box 169, Folder 628)
    - Industrial Exhausters (Box 169, Folder 629)
    - Instruction Booklets (Box 169, Folder 630)
    - J (Box 169, Folder 631)
    - K (Box 169, Folder 632)
    - L (Box 170, Folder 633-634)
    - Letters, Miscellaneous (Box 170, Folder 635)
    - M (Box 170, Folder 636-637)
    - N (Box 170, Folder 638)
    - O (Box 170, Folder 639)
    - P (Box 170, Folder 640-641)
    - Pressure Pipes (Box 170, Folder 642)
    - R (Box 171, Folder 643-644)
    - S (Box 171, Folder 645-649)
    - T (Box 171, Folder 650)
    - U (Box 171, Folder 651)
    - V (Box 171, Folder 652)
    - W (Box 172, Folder 653-659)
    - X - Z (Box 173, Folder 660)
    - General Supply Catalogs
      - Parts (Box 173, Folder 661)
      - Unsorted (Box 173, Folder 662-670)
      - Chicago Bridge & Iron Company (Box 174, Folder 671)
      - Lyon Metal Production, Inc. (Box 174, Folder 672)
      - Matthews Equipment Company (Box 174, Folder 673)
      - Murphy Paint Corporation (Box 174, Folder 674)
      - Myco Products (Box 174, Folder 675)
      - Steamaire Company (Box 174, Folder 676-677)
      - Unsorted (Box 174, Folder 678-685)
      - Blueprints (Box 175)
    - Mr. Chenail Card Room Notebook (Box 176, Folder 686)
    - Price Book, Daily Aide (Box 176, Folder 687)
  - Subseries F: Production Reports and Analyses, 1915-1956
    - Cotton Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 432, Folder 1-2)
    - Product and Cost of Manufacturing
      - 1915-1916 (Box 177, Folder 688)
      - 1917-1918 (Box 177, Folder 689)
      - 1919 (Box 177, Folder 690)
      - 1920 (Box 177, Folder 691)
      - 1921 (Box 177, Folder 692)
      - 1922 (Box 177, Folder 693)
      - 1923 (Box 177, Folder 694)
      - 1953 (Box 176, Folder 698)
      - 1931 (Box 432, Folder 3)
      - 1951 (Box 172, Folder 696)
      - 1952 (Box 176, Folder 697)
      - 1953 (Box 176, Folder 698)
      - 1953 (Box 432, Folder 4)
    - Reports
      - Form 9, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 699)
      - Form 15-P, 1950 (Box 176, Folder 700)
      - A-142, 148; 61/2 02 Oxford (Box 176, Folder 701)
      - AD-273, 292, 302; Government Twill (Box 176, Folder 702)
      - AD-300, 317' 63" Duck (Box 176, Folder 703)
      - AD-320 72" Duck (Box 176, Folder 704)
      - American Cotton Manufacturing Institute (Box 176, Folder 705)
      - Form C-1, 1951 (Box 176, Folder 706)
      - Cost Analysis, 1955 (Box 176, Folder 707)
      - Form M15A, 1950 (Box 176, Folder 708)
      - Form M15C, 1947, 1950 (Box 176, Folder 709)
      - Form M15J, 1945, 1950-1951 (Box 176, Folder 710)
      - Sizing and Seconds, 1952, 1955-1956 (Box 176, Folder 711)
      - Form TLA 1, 2, 1942 (Box 176, Folder 712)
      - Product Testing, 1954 (Box 176, Folder 713)
      - U.S. Bureau of Census, Industrial Division Reports, 1956 (Box 176, Folder 714)
      - U.S. Testing (Box 176, Folder 715)
      - WPB 295, 1942, 1945 (Box 176, Folder 716)
      - WPB 638, 1942 (Box 176, Folder 717)
      - WPB 658-B, 1942, 1949 (Box 176, Folder 718)
      - WPB 658-C, 1942, 1949 (Box 176, Folder 719)
      - WPB 658-E, 1943, 1945 (Box 176, Folder 720)
  - Subseries G: Production Records, undated, 1866-1957
    - Record Books
      - 1854-1861 (Box 176, Folder 721)
      - 1863-1870 (Box 176, Folder 722)
      - 1874-1875 (Box 176, Folder 723)
      - 1922 (Box 176, Folder 724)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 176, Folder 725)
    - Loom Orders, 1939-1942 (Box 176, Folder 726)
    - Bailing Record, 1866-1867 (Box 178)
    - Bleaching Book, 1886-1894 (Box 179)
    - Bleaching Book, 1892-1899 (Box 180)
    - Bleaching Book, 1896-1899 (Box 181)
    - Weaving Reports, 1933-1935 (Box 182)
    - Drapes, 1929-1931 (Box 183)
    - Weaving Pattern Charts, undated
      - 6180-7000 (Box 184, Folder 727)
      - 7795-7799 (Box 184, Folder 728)
      - Chain Drafts 7701-7799 (Box 184, Folder 729)
      - 6129-6149 (Box 184, Folder 730)
      - 7757-7769 (Box 184, Folder 731)
      - 7747-7756 (Box 184, Folder 732)
      - 7710-7719 (Box 184, Folder 733)
      - 7737-7746 (Box 184, Folder 734)
      - 7790-7794 (Box 184, Folder 735)
      - 7780-7789 (Box 184, Folder 736)
      - 6100-6128 (Box 184, Folder 737)
      - 7719-7727 (Box 184, Folder 738)
      - 7728-7736 (Box 184, Folder 739)
      - 7768-7779 (Box 184, Folder 740)
      - 6150-6178 (Box 184, Folder 741)
      - Chain Drafts 6400-6496 (Box 184, Folder 742)
      - 6416-6426 (Box 184, Folder 743)
      - 6400-6415 (Box 184, Folder 744)
      - 6427-6437 (Box 184, Folder 745)
      - 6438-6445 (Box 184, Folder 746)
      - 6446-6469 (Box 184, Folder 747)
      - 6470-6498 (Box 184, Folder 748)
      - Chain Drafts 7400-7706 (Box 184, Folder 749)
      - 7458-7499 (Box 184, Folder 750)